statshow.com 2017-12-03

# StatShow - Privacy

### Our Privacy Policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by using our feedback form. At StatShow, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by statshow.com and how it is used.

### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, statshow.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

statshow.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense.  
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on statshow.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  
statshow.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. statshow.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.  
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

### Google Ads

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/).
